The movie that leaves all other sequels behind!
Bugs Bunny's 3rd Movie: 1001 Rabbit Tales is a animation,
comedy, family film directed by Chuck Jones.
If Bugs Bunny were to direct his signature inquiry--"What's
up, doc?"--toward the modern-day Warner Bros.
creative team, he wouldn't be far off.
For 1001 Rabbit Tales, they've doctored up a batch of classic cartoons featuring the carrot muncher and
his bumbling comrades and bundled them, near seamlessly, into a feature-length film.
Here's the premise: Bugs and Daffy, both book salesmen, are
competing to sell the most copies of a kids' book.
Instead of burrowing a beeline to his sales territory (he should have made a left at
Albuquerque), Bugs ends up in the castle of Yosemite Sam, here a harem-leading honcho.
Sam's pain-in-the-spurs son, Prince Abalaba, needs somebody to read him stories; Bugs, who'd sooner
take the job than suffer the alternative, that involving being boiled in oil, signs on.
Bugs Bunny / Daffy Duck / Porky Pig / Yosemite Sam / Sylvester / Sylvester, Jr. / Speedy Gonzales / Tweety / Genie
/ Hassan / Big Bad Wolf / Beanstalk Giant / Elvis Gorilla / Stork (voice), played by Mel Blanc.
Witch Hazel (voice), played by Bea Benaderet.
Elmer Fudd (voice), played by Arthur Q. Bryan.
Granny / Mother Gorilla / Goldimouse (voice), played by June Foray.
Old Storyteller (voice), played by Shepard Menken.
Prince Abba-Dabba (voice), played by Lennie Weinrib.
Bugs Bunny's 3rd Movie: 1001 Rabbit Tales (also known as Bugs Bunny's 1001 Rabbit Tales) is a
1982 American animated fantasy comedy film produced and directed by Friz Freleng.
It combines classic Warner Bros.
cartoon shorts with new animation, with Bugs Bunny serving as the story host.
The film explores themes of cartoon, compilation, package film.
The tone is lighthearted.